Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS 213
Fales Library and Special Collections
Peter Dougherty Collection
Bulk, 1974-1987
1965-2001
MSS 213
Fales Library and Special Collections
12.0 linear feet (16 boxes)
Peter Dougherty is a marketing professional with extensive international experience, including working with MTV from its early days. The Peter Dougherty Collection documents American and British punk rock and hip hop, in addition to Dougherty's work with MTV, and includes audiovisual materials, ephemera, flyers, production manuscripts, and promotional materials.
Arrangement
Paper materials are arranged either chronologically or alphabetically. The collection is arranged into the following five series:
Series I: Audio
Series II: Video
Series III: MTV and Music Business
Subseries A: Branding and Programming
Subseries B: Artist Files
Series IV: Ephemera, Flyers, Programs
Subseries A: Music
Subseries B: Art
Subseries C: Animation and Film
Series V: Personal
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
Scope and Content
The Peter Dougherty Collection preserves audio and video recordings documenting British and American punk rock and hip hop. The collection is largely Dougherty's personal music-related collection, from the years before he became a marketing professional. The collection also preserves marketing literature, business manuals, production manuscripts for artists Beastie Boys and Run-D.M.C., in addition to awards programs that document Dougherty's work with MTV Europe. This acquisition also includes Dougherty's personal collection of New York and London art, music, and film events ephemera and promotional materials from the late 1970s through the 1990s.
Biographical Note
Peter Dougherty was born in Queens, NY in 1955, and attended his first rock concert at Shea Stadium during the summer of 1966. After witnessing the madness of The Beatles he then saw Simon and Garfunkel the following summer, and from there, Janis Joplin, The Byrds, Sly and The Family Stone,The Allman Brothers Band, etc. By the mid 1970s, once he was old enough to gain admittance, he starting attending clubs such as Max's Kansas City, CBGB, and Club 82, and began recording these shows.
He later began working with his brother Paul and other friends videotaping bands, and as an assistant in the first 'video lounges' at Peppermint Lounge and Danceteria. In 1982 he started as a production assistant in MTV's creative/promotional department, and remained there until 1990 when he moved to London to become Creative Director of MTV Europe.
Provenance
The collection was acquired by the Fales Library from Peter Dougherty in 2008.
Separated Materials
Printed materials, including zines, have been removed from the collection and will be cataloged as part of the Fales Downtown Book Collection.
Beastie Boys.; Hell, Richard; Raincoats.; Run-D.M.C. (Musical group).; Smith, Patti; Television (Musical group).; Voidoids (Musical group).; Alternative rock music.; Art |v Exhibitions.; Audiocassettes.; Graffiti artists; Graffiti.; Music business |z New York; Music |x Competitions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Music |x Social aspects.; Music |x Societies, etc. |z New York (State) |z New York.; Musicians |y 1990-2000.; Postcards.; Posters.; Programs (documents); Punk culture |z New York (State) |z New York.; Punk rock music.; Rap (Music)|x History and criticism.; Rock music |z United States |y 1991-2000.; Scripts (documents)
- Series I: Audio
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open to researchers. Appointments are necessary for the use of manuscript and archival collections.
  Some audiovisual materials have not been preserved and are not currently available to researchers.
  - Subseries A: Audio, 1776-1785
    Access copies may not be available for all items. Please contact Fales with questions about access or to make appointment.
    - PA Spot, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0001)
      Scope and Content
      Content: Unknown
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Format: 1/4 in. Audiocassette
      Tape Length: 90 minutes
      Access CD available by appointment only.
    - [1]-- Gang War at Fast Lane, Asbury Park NY, September 30 [2]-- J [Hanson] at [Bottomline], July 20, 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0002)
      Content: Two sets
      Side A: Ramblin Rose, London Boys, These Boots, Steppin Stone
      Side B: Cant Put Your Arms, Harder, Laughin at [lu], Big Kiss
    - Gang War at MUD, November 27, 1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0003)
      Content:
      Ramblin Rose, London, MIA, Endless Party, I'll Go Crazy, Be with the Boys, Harder
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request Part 1 and Part 2.
    - Big Audio Dynamite- Megatop Phoenix, June 14, 1989 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0004)
      Side A: Start; Rewind; All Mink and No Manners; Union, Jack; Contact; Dragon Town; Baby Don’t Apologize; Is Yours Working Yet?; Around the Girl in 80 Ways
      Side B: James Brown; Everybody Needs a Holiday; Mick's a Hippie Burning; House Arrest; The Green Lady; London Bridge; Stalag 123; End
      There is no access CD available for researchers at this time. Please contact a Fales archivist.
    - [1] -- Big Audio Dynamite live, Paradiso, Amsterdam, March 23, 1990 [2]--Alexandria Palace, London, August 10, 1990 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0005)
      Side A: Paradiso, Amsterdam 3-23-90 Columbia Records 1991 Demo CD.
      Side B: Alexandra Palace, London 8-10-90 *note: most M. Jones solos edited and remixed by M. Jones & N. Hawkins
      Tape Length: 60 minutes
    - Big Audio Dynamite - [1]-- Capital Radio, [December 4, 1985] [2]--WNEW December 13, 1985, December 4, 1985/ December 13, 1985 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0006)
      Side A (Dec 4, 1985): unknown
      Side B: Gary Crowley
    - Gang War at Fast Lane, December 2, 1979, 12/2/1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0007)
      Side A: Courageous Cat, Ramblin Rose, London Boys, These Boots, Endless Party, Harder, 10 Commandments, Wayne Still Hates, MIA, Hey Thanks, Pipeline.
      Side B: Just Because, Round & Round, Great Big Kiss, I'll Go Crazy, Can't Put Your Arms, Gypsy, I Can Tell, Courageous Cat
    - Gang War at Heat, December 28, 1979, 12/28/1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0008)
      Content: One Set
      Pipeline, Rambling Rose, London, Endless Party, MIA, Harder They Come, I'll Go Crazy, Rather Be With the Boys, Wayne Still Hates, Little Bit a Whore, Great Big Kiss, Hey Thanx, Can't Put Your Arms, Courageous Cat
    - New York Telephone, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0009)
      Tape Length: 30 minutes
    - Mick & Co '85, 1985 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0010)
    - Howard Stern, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0011)
      Tape Length: Unknown
    - CaMoy Shalls II, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0012)
    - CaMoy Shalls, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0013)
      [Music], Skin [CreAm], Ad. Bed, Crime Comp., Porcilona, Iron, Bed, Decaf Husband, Without Warning, Rely, Windmill, Drums
    - Hip-Hop (A+B) [Rommi Bop!], undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0014)
    - "Tastes So Good" File 13, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0015)
      Tape Length: 10 minutes
    - Gang War - Trude Heller, December 29, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0017)
    - [1]-- "I Like to Watch" Double D & Steinski [2]-- Wild Style, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0018)
    - Gang War - Trude Heller's, December 29, 1979 [EMPTY CASE] (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0019)
      Contents: One set
      Courageous Cat-cut, Ramblin Rose-cut, Pipeline, Ramblin Rose, London, I'll Go Crazy, Rather Be with the Boys, Endless Party, Harder They Come, Wayne Still Hates, In Every Little Girl, Just Because I'm White
      [EMPTY CASE]
    - [1]-- MTV Networks, February 11, 1987 [2]-- [Talking] Heads, 1983, 1983, 1987 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0020)
      Tape Length: 120 minutes
    - [1]-- Bottom Line [2]-- BAD, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0021)
      Side A: Bottom Line; BAD -US 12" Remix/Bottom Line; BAD -British 12" versions
    - OPAL- "Early Recordings," Serpent Records, 1989 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0022)
      Side A: Empty Box Blues, She's a Diamond, My Only Friend, Empty Bottles, Grains of Sand, Brigit on Sunday
      Side B: Northern Line, Strange Delight, Fell From the Sun, Harriet Brown, Lulabye, All souls
      Tape Length: 53 minutes
    - Smokescreens- by J.T.C., Chick Publications, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0023)
      Content: 1982 By Jack T. Chick
      Tape Length: 100 minutes
    - untitled, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0024)
    - [1]-- Double Dee & Steinski "Hip-Hop Mix" January 1985 [2]-- "Repo Man" The Ig + opening (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0025)
      Side A: "Hip-Hop" Mix Side B: "Repo Man" the Ig and Opening
    - [1]-- Beastie Boys- Spots [2]-- Beastie Ads, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0026)
    - VO Disco August 1981 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0027)
      Side A: with VO and without VO
    - [1]-- Double D + Steinski "Payoff Mix" [2]-- Fantasy Three "It's Your Rock", undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0028)
      Side A: Payoff Mix
      Side B: It's Your Rock
      Tape Length: 20 minutes
      Access CD available for researchers by appointment only.
    - [1]-- Akabu "Watch Yourself" (inst) [2]-- Lesson 2 Double Dee + Steinski, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0029)
      Side A: Akabu "Watch Yourself" (instrumental)
      Side B: Lesson 2 Double Dee + Steinski
    - Changin Times Jazz Party '82 Union League Club, New York City, October 7, 1982 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0030)
      Side A: A Change in the Weather, Ain't Misbehavin', Indiana, Cherry, My Blue Heaven
      Side B: I Got Rhythm, I Want a Little Girl, Sheik of Araby, Take the "A" Train
    - [1]-- Alan Squat [&] w/ stilleto [2]-- Steading Clubs 7 December 4? 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0031)
    - Blue Humans at Max's March 19, 1979/ Rev (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0032)
      Side A: Blue Humans Max's March 19, 1979 / Rev
      Side B: Rev
    - Alan at Max's July 18, 1980, 7/18/1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0033)
      Content: Two Sets, Unknown
    - [1]-- Miles Davis at A. Fisher Hall, Live, July 5, 1981 [2]-- Suicide-MS Lunch at Chase Park October 31st 1981, July 5, 1981/October 31, 1981 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0034)
      Side A: Miles Davis July 5, 1981, A. Fisher Hall
      Side B: Suicide/MS Lunch Chase Park October 31, 1981
    - Alan NYE/T.V./Alan/Jan2 Trudie 81 Trudy Hellers New Years Eve -80-81, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0035)
      Side A: Crazy Maniacs, Kung Fu Cowboy, Aint that Nothing
      Side B: Fireball, Kung Fu Cowboy, Jukebox Babe, Heartbeat
    - [1]-- Suicide at Rock Lounge, December 20, 1980 [2]-- Danceteria, August 1, 1980, 12/20/1980, 8/1/1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0036)
      Side A: Crazy Maniacs, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Night time, Sweet White Lady, 96 Tears
      Side B: BeBop Kid, Staying Alive, Fast Money Music/Ghost Rider, Sweetheart, Touch Me, Harlem, BeBop Kid, Stayin Alive
    - Alan Max's Doc May 8, 1981, 5/8/1981 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0037)
    - Suicide '80 Max's Jan 18 '80, 2 Sets, 1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0038)
      Content: Two Sets
      Side A: Harlem, Radiation, Dream Baby Dream, Ghost Rider
      Side B: Dance, 96 Tears, Rocket USA
      Tape Length: 90 mintues
    - [1]-- Suicide Hurrah, December 18, 1979 [2]-- Suicide Heat, February 29, 1980, December 18, 1979, February 29, 1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0039)
      Side A: Nightime, Ghost Rider, Dream Baby Dream, Radiation, Harlem, Sweetheart
      Side B: Ghost Rider, Harlem, Sweetheart, Radiation, Rocket U.S.A.
    - [1]-- Suicide Oct 1 '80 Hurrah 1 show [2]-- Suicide Rock Homage 1 show Oct 10 '80, October 1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0040)
      Side A: Harlem, Ghost Rider, Cheree, Crazy Maniacs, Radiation, Sweet Little Lady, [RnR]
      Side B: Rocket USA, Crazy Maniacs, Cheree, Harlem, Ghost Rider, RnR is My Life, Sweet White Lady
    - [1]--- Alan Vega Rock City Rock City Dec 26th 1980 [2]--Alan Vega Trude Heller Jan 3 1981, 12/26/80, 1/3/81 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0041)
      Side A: Crazy Maniacs, Kung Fu Cowboy, Love Cry, ByeBye Bayou, Heartbeat, Juke Box Baby, Savage [Mudd] [or]/Niteclub
      Side B. Kung Fu Cowboy, Fireball, Hearbeat, Vietnam Alan, Jukebox Babe
    - Suicide Max's Dec 28th '78/CBGB June 2 '79 second set, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0042)
      Side A: Dance. Four Horsemen, Keep Your Dreams, Harlem/Las Vegas, Ray, Sweetheart, (Cont'd), Ghost Rider, Frankie, Johnny
      Side B: Frankie, Dance, Johnny, 96 Tears, Che
    - [1]-- Suicide June May '79 [2]-- CBGB June 2 '79 2nd set/ May '79, 1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0043)
      Side A: Frankie, Dance, Johnny, 96 Tears, Che, Las Vegas, Keep your Dreams, Radiation
    - Suicide Hurrah April 11 '80, 1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0044)
      Side A: Dance, [Track Unknown], [Track Unknown], Sweetheart, Las Vegas
    - [1]-- Suicide Pepermint Lounge Jan 9 '81 [2]-- Ritz with Suicide April 24, 1981 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0045)
      Side A: Rock n' Roll, Crazy Maniacs, Dream Baby Dream, Sweet White Lady, Ghost Rider, Harlem
    - Rev Hurrah 6/11/80, 1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0046)
    - [1]-- Suicide May/July 77 CBGB 5/4/77 Max's 7/9/77 2 sets [2]-- Rev Feb. 25 1979 Max's, 1977, 1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0047)
      Side A: Ghost Rider, 96 Tears, [Track Unknown], Rocket USA, [Track Unknown], Ghost Rider
      Side B: Fever, Kansas City, [Track Unknown]
    - [1]-- Suicide Mudd Dec 24 '80 [2]-- Suicide Cont'd "80s" Dec 26, '80, 1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0048)
      Side A and Side B: Night Time, Ghost Rider, Cheree, Sweet White Lady, Rock n Roll, Night Time, Ave. A, Keep Your Dreams
    - Suicide Thursday (2), Friday (1) CBGB Nov 2 '78, Nov 3 '78, 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0049)
      Side A: Mr. Ray, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Harlem, Night Time, Touch Me- Nice, Las Vegas
      Side B: Four Horsemen, Ghost Rider, [Track Unknown], Ghost Rider, Jesus 4.Four Horsemen, Rocket U.S.A.
    - Suicide '80's Friday the 13th/ June 13 '80 one set, 1980 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0050)
      Side A: Harlem, Ghost Rider, Sweetheart, Rocket U.S.A., Touch Me
    - [1]-- Suicide Mudd 2 Feb 7, 1979 Stealing-Suicide-Van [2]--Alan Annie- Mudd (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0051)
      Side A (Hound Dog): Dance, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Harlem
    - [1]-- Suicide Irving Plaza Jan 24 '81 [2]-- Pepermint Lounge April?, January 24, 1981 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0052)
      Side A: Rock n Roll, Crazy Maniacs, Cheree, Sweet White Lady, Ghost Rider
    - Suicide July 24, 26, 27 '78 Music Machine London, July 24, 26, 27, 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0053)
      Side A and B: Ghost Rider, Rocket USA, Dance, Harlem, Cheree, Ghost Rider, Rocket USA, 96 Tears, Harlem, Ghost Rider, Rocket USA
    - Suicide CBGB June 1 '79, June 1, 1979 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0054)
      Side A: Touch Me, Ghost Rider, Keep Your Dreams, Las Vegas, Four Horsemen (Radiation)
      Side B: Keep Your Dreams (studio), Rocket U.S.A., Night Time, 96 Tears, Sister Ray, Harlem
    - Suicide July 24, 26, 27 Music Machine, undated (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0055)
      Side A and B: Ghost Rider, Rochet U.S.A., Dance, Harlem, Cheree, Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., 96 Tears, Harlem, Ghost Rider, Rocket U.S.A., Dance, Frankie, Cheree, Sister Ray
    - B-52's/Suicide Nova semiotext(e) 17 Irving Place Friday Dec 1, 1978, December 1, 1978 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0056)
      Side A: Lava, Moon in the Sky, 6060-842, Runnin Around, Rock Lobster, Downtown, 52 Girls, Hero Worship, Devil's in My Car
      Side B: Planet, Harlem, Mama Mama, Sweetheart
    - Waldo Steding 4/79 CBGB April 4, 1979/ 3/81 Ritz March 12, 1981, 1979, 1981 (Box 1, Media ID: 213.0057)
      Side A: [Track Unknown], Get Ready, Wake up Mixed Up
    - Jerks/DNA/Dark Day/Blue Humans/Contortions/8 Eyed Spy/Alan+Annie/Rev/Suicide (1977-1979) (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0058)
      Side A and B: [1] Jerks w/ James - Max's 8-9-77, DNA 3-11-78 1st perf. [2] Jerks 4-17-79 Maxs, DNA 5-27-79 CBGB, Dark Day 6-13-79 Mud Club [3] Blue Humans 3-19-79 3 trax, Contortions 7-13-78 2 trax, 8 Eyed Spy 12-6-79 2 Trax [4] Alan+Annie 6-13-79 Mud Club, Rev 2-25-79 Maxs, Suicide 2-4-78 CBGB
    - James White & the Contortions, Club 57, Feb 2, 1979, February 2, 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0059)
      Side A: Contort Yourself, Tropical Heatwave, Jaded Side B: Contort Yourself
    - Tom Verlaine, RITZ Oct 8 1981, October 8, 1981 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0060)
      Side A: Kingdom Come, Red Leaves, Souvenir from a Dream
      Side B: Marquee Moon
      Tape Length: Tape Length
    - Television/ John [Cale] New Year's Eve Palladium NYC Dec 31st 1976/ Jan 1st 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0061)
      Side A: Satisfaction, Fire Engine, Friction, Elevation, Little Johnny Jewel, Adventure, Knockin, Kingdom Come
      Side B: Kingdom Come, Helen of Troy, You Know More Than I Know, Paris 1919, Darling I Need You, Guts, Fear
    - T.V., Max's, Oct 27 '76, sets 1 & 2, First of 2 nites, October 27, 1976 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0062)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Judy, Marquee Moon, Friction, Torn Curtain, Breakin' In my Heart, Hard on Love, Prove it, Venus
      Side B: Venus cont'd, Little Johnny Jewel, Foxhole, Kingdom Come
    - Television, CBGB Dec 7, 1975. 2 sets, copy, December 7, 1975 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0063)
      Tom Verlaine- lead vocals, guitar; Richard Lloyd- guitar, backing vocals; Billy Feeca- drums; Fred Smith- bass, backing vocals
      Side A and B: Fire Engine, Prove It, Oh [Mi] Amore*, Torn Curtain, Let Me Out*, Marquee Moon, See No Evil*, Venus De Milo, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Guiding Light*, Kingdom Come *First's/Tape-->Paul"M"/w/Talking Heads
      Format: 1/4 in. audiocassette
    - Television - Mother's, Oct 18th 1975, October 18, 1975 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0064)
      Tom Verlaine- guitar, vocals; Richard Lloyd- guitar; Billy Fecca- drums; Fred Smith-bass
      Side A: Fire Engine, Judy Said, Marquee Moon, Friction, Torn Curtain, Breakin In My Heart.
      Side B: Venus de Milo, Foxhole, Prove It, Poor Circulation, Little Johnny Jewel, Hard On Love, Kingdom Come ?
    - Doc Steding '80s Nov 7th 1980, two sets, November 7, 1980 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0065)
      Side A: You Got it, Chase the Dragon, The Joke, (Hound Dog)
    - Paradise Garage: Jerk- Contortions- Hell, Sunday June 18th 1978 -Father's Day, June 18, 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0066)
      Side A: Dish It Out, My Infatuation, Roving Eye, Flip Your Face, Can't Stand Myself, Jaded, Contort Yourself
      Side B: Down at the RnR club, Sports, Kid With the Replaceable Head, Staring in Her Eyes, You’ve Gotta Lose, Another World, Liars Beware, Blank
    - Contortions July 13 CBGB/ July 14 Millenium - 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0067)
      George- bass, Jody- guitar, Patti- slide guitar
      Side A and B: Roving Eye, My Infatuation, Contort Yourself, Throw Me Away, Jaded But So in Love, Contort Yourself
    - Glen's Desperation Benefit, Mudd, Nov 20 1980, November 20, 1980 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0068)
    - Teenage Jesus and the Jerks w/ J. Sigfried: Nov 15 1977- Max's only set, Jan 13 1978- CBGB two sets., 1977, 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0069)
      Side A: Three Jerks Sets
      Side B: Jerks with James
    - Doc & The Boys, Heat, March 14 '80, March 14, 1980 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0070)
      Content: TV Party - Doc & The Boys
    - Steding, Hurrah - Sept [24] 1979; 8 Eyed Spy - Max's Dec 6 1979 (one set only) (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0071)
      Side A: Steding Hurrah Sep 24, '79; Suicide Midnight Special
      Side B: 8-eyed Spy Max's Dec 6, '79, one set only
    - Tirez Tirez Live (Inroads) June 12 '81/ Savage T.V. Party, Easter '81 [Pep Lounge?], 1981 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0072)
    - Doc Trax Dec 3 '80 plus Suicide 80s excerpts & 2 sets slides show soundtrack, 1980 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0073)
    - Contortions- CBGB 1st set 2/4/78. Blessed- Maxs March 5th 1978 1st set. Fleshtones- CBGB 2/4/78 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0074)
      Side A: I Don’t Wanna Be Happy, My infatuation
    - X Magazine Benefit, Millenium E. 4th st * Erasers w/Quinne - Screamers, CBGB Nove 17th '78, November 17, 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0075)
      Side A: Funtime*, DNA, Roving Eye, Love Twice Removed
      Side B: (Contortions Cont'd); Throw Me Away, Jaded But So in Love, Content Yourself, SCREAMERS
    - Contortions 2/78 April 24, 1978 Max's/ New Aug 22 '79 Max's, Apr 24, 1979, Aug 22, 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0076)
      Side A: Dish It Out, My Infatuation, I Don't Wanna Be Happy
      Side B: Good Times
    - Contortions Max's Jan 28 '79/ DNA Jerks CBGB Jan 17 '79/ T.J. and the Jerks, Jerks Again Max's May 15 '79, 1979 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0077)
    - Contortions Thanksgiving '78 Nov. 23 Max's one set only, November 23, 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0078)
      Side A and B: [Track Unknown], My Infatuation, I Don't Wanna Be Happy, [Track Unknown], Designed to Kill, [Track Unknown], Roving Eye, Love Twice Removed, Dish It Out, Disposable You, Throw Me Away, Jaded But So in Love, Contort Yourself
    - Contortions Jam Aug 17 '78/ Chain of Fools Soundcheck Max's 2 sets Jam, August 17, 1978 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0079)
      Content: [Can't] Take it, Please Please Me
      [Track Unknown], Dish It Out, My Infatuation, Designed to Kill, Love Twice Removed, I Don't Wanna Be Happy, [Track Unknown], Throw Me Away, Contort Yourself, Can't Stand
    - Valore- The Martini Room, 1994 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0080)
      To Love and Be Loved, The Martini Room, Love, Mr. Lucky, The Quiet Time, Cryin', I Wish I'd Never, Fly Hindenberg, Two Ships, All The Time Blues, River
      Tape Length: 92 minutes
      CD currently unavailable.
    - Shame on you, Aerosmith/ Apache-Tequila, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0081)
      Tape Length: 70 minutes
    - Untitled, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0082)
    - Alan Vega, 1983 (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0083)
      Content: Molson Golden Fall '83
      Border Crossing, Astronauts, Wine Steward, Camping, Bar, Skiing, Musicians (Concert), Airplane
    - Less Than Zero, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0084)
      Side A: Rocking Pneumonia And the Boogie Woogie Flu/Aerosmith, Lite Fades Away/Roy Orbision, Rock And Roll All Nite/Poison, Goin' Back To Cali/L.L. Cool J., You and Me(Less Than Zero)/Glen Danzig, In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida/Slayer
      Side B: Bring the Noise/Public Enemy, Are You My Woman/Black Flames, She's Lost You/Joan Jett and the Blackhearts, How to Love Again/Oran Juice Jones and Alyson Williams, Hazy Shade of Winter/Bangles
    - Apes of God - Jeroen Wilhelmus, Michiel Hofmans, Meinbert v Soest, Jacky Simons, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0085)
    - SWEET/ MEATMEN and other classic muscle tunes, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0086)
      Side A: Sweet- Fox on the Run, Ballroom Blitz, Action, Someone Else Will; Uriah Heep- Easy Livin; Nazareth- Razamanaz; Meatmen- War of the Superbikes; Dictators- Master Race Rock; Amboy Dukes- Journey to the Center of the Mind; Judas Priest- Steeler; Lucifers Friend- Ride the Sky- Butthole Surfers- Sweatloaf
      Side B: Meatmen- Punkerama, Cum On Over To My Crib, Lesbian Death Dirge, Pillar of Sodom, Centurians of Rome, God's Bullies, Cadaver Class, French People Suck, Wine Wenches Wheels, What's this Shit Called Love, Dance to the Music, Rock + Roll Juggernaut - Tesco's solo EP
    - Jean Caffeine, undated (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0087)
      Side A: Big Wheel, Hushed Tones, Jesus is Coming Soon (to a theatre near you), That was the Liquor Talkin'
    - Feelies Maxwell's Sunday April 13 1980/ Feelies 2nd Set (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0088)
    - Feelies Sept- Dec 1978 Max's Sept 2nd 1978 (late show)/ Hurrah Dec 12th 1978 (one set) (Box 2, Media ID: 213.0089)
      Side A: Boy, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, Loveless Love, Work, Original Love, [Track Unknown], Crazy Rhythms, Well Alright, Third Ucle
      Side B: Boy, Original Love, Work, Loveless Love, Fa Ce La, Moscow Nights, [Track Unknown]